Guide to J. Hugo Aronson papers 1924-1968
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Governor
  - Correspondence General
    - G (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Gerard, James, Clerk of Court Glacier County; Gerlough, Wilma; Toole County Republican Central Committee; A. L. Gleason, Great Falls Clinic; Greenlee, Betty; Gribble, Paul), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 4)
    - H (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include O. R. Hagen, Vice-President Traders State Bank; Robert Haines, Haines Public Drug; Mack Hamilton, Cascade County Republican Central Committee; B. M. Harris, President Yellowstone Bank; Matt Himsl, Chairman Flathead County Republic Central Committee), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 5)
    - I-J (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Ernest Immel; Elizabeth Ireland; Joseph Iten, Representative Ravalli County; E. L. Johnson, First National Bank of Plains; D. L. Casey Jones, Montana Shannon Mining Co.; O. M. Jorgenson, President Security Trust and Savings Bank), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 6)
    - Inaugural Festival Committee, National, 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 7)
    - K (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include George Kern, Absaroka Conservation Committee; Glayds E. Knowles; member of Republican National Committee for Montana; Horace Koessler, Intermountain Lumber Co.; Max Kuhr), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 8)
    - L (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Leo J. Lamberson, Supreme Vice President Order of Ahepa; Glenn Larson, Senator Sanders County; Albert Leuthold; E. H. Lindstrom, Montana Medical Association; R. J. Losleben, Valley Drug Co.; G. O. Lowe, Montana Flour Mills Co.), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 9)
    - M (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include N. B. Matthews, President Basin State Bank; H. G. Mebust, President First National Bank of Kalispell; Lee Metcalf, Montana Congressman; Earl Moritz, Hi-Way Motor Freight Co.; G. F. Mundy, Gildford Roller Mill; Rod Murchison, Service Plumbing and Heating Co.), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 10)
    - N (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include National Safety Council; Matt Newell, Charter Oil Co.; Kenny Newton, Newton Motors; Northern Montana College; Northwest Mining Association;), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 11)
    - O-P (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Clarence H. Olson, The American Legion; H. E. Olsson, Ronan State Bank; Winfield Page, Missoula County Representative; E. A, Phillips, Secretary Montana Stockgrowers Association, Inc.; W. E. Pierce, Chairman of the Republican County Central Committee), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 12)
    - R (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include A. J. Rasmussen, Rasmussen Farming Corporation; Republican National Committee; Harry C. W. Richter, Livestock Sanitary Board; John Rice, Rice Truck Lines; Thomas Ross, Senator Blaine County), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 13)
    - S (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Sacred Heart Hospital; T. J. Sillers, First National Bank of Whitefish; Elmer Sorensen, Yellowstone Mercantile Co.; Wynn Sparr, Robertson Petroleum Co.; Ralph L. Starr, Mayor of Missoula), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 14)
    - T-Z (primarily congratulations on election; correspondents include Harry Todd, Petroleum County Manager; K. P. Todd, Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Co.; Toole County Republican Central Committee; John Travis, Havre Daily News; United Press Association; C. M. Wall, President Montana Chamber of Commerce; John Willard, Montana Record Publishing Co.; A. R. Wilson, Texas Co.; W. J. Winters, Senator Ravalli County), 1952 (Box-folder 9 / 15)
    - A (correspondents include Einar Andersson, Svenska Amerikanaren Tribunen; James Austin, Mayor of Great Falls; L. R. Austin, Big Horn Supply Inc.), 1953 (Box-folder 9 / 16)
    - Appointments: Advisory Board of Pardons and Paroles, 1953 (Box-folder 9 / 17)
    - Appointments: Board of Barber Examiners, 1953 (Box-folder 9 / 18)
    - Appointments: Board of Equalization, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 9 / 19)
    - Appointments: Board of Examiners, Accountancy, 1953 (Box-folder 9 / 20)
    - Appointments: Columbia Compact Commission, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 1)
    - Appointments: Fireman; Veteran's Administration Building, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 2)
    - Appointments: Hail Insurance Board, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 3)
    - Appointments: Labor and Industry, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 4)
    - Appointments: Legislative Council, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 5)
    - Appointments: Liquor Control Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 10 / 6)
    - Appointments: Milk Control Board, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 7)
    - Appointments: Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 10 / 8)
    - Appointments: Personnel Commission, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 9)
    - Appointments: Public Employee Retirement System, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 10)
    - Appointments: State Land Office, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 11)
    - Appointments: Stenographer, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 12)
    - Appointments: Teachers Retirement System, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 13)
    - Appointments: Training School, Boulder, 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 14)
    - Appointments: Treasurer, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 10 / 15)
    - B-C (correspondents include D. W. Buckman, Assistant Vice President the First National Bank St. Paul; Ken Byerly, Byerly Publishing Co.; Elizabeth Connelly, President Montana Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs; Frank Connelly), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 16)
    - D-G (correspondents include Wesley D'Ewart, Montana Congressman; E. L. Dorsett, Superintendent Northwestern Improvement Co.; C. Pat Egan, Manager Hotel Finlen; Dwight D. Eisenhower, President of the United States; S. H. Finger, Vice President National Park Bank; Henry Fowler, Defense Production Administration; Roz Goodman, Chairman Young Republican County central Committee; R. G. Glatz, Winnett Times), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 17)
    - H-K (correspondents include Havre Independent; Norman J. Holter; R. E. Huelster, President Gallatin County Women's Republican Club; Millo Jensen, Chairman Lake County Republican Central Committee; G. H. Kern, Absaroka Conservation Committee; J. F. Kumpf), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 18)
    - L-N (correspondents include J. Russell Larcombe, Phillips County News; H. L. Lund, President of First National Bank; A. G. Martin, Standard Oil Co.; Paul McCormick, Chairman Yellowstone County Republican Central Committee; Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company; Homer Murphy, Flathead Courier; New Rainbow Mining Co.; Donald Nyquist, Court Reporter ), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 19)
    - O-S (correspondents include Walter Olson, President Valley Motor Supply Co.; Oliver Powell, President Federal Reserve Bank of Minneapolis; Robert Roush, Secretary Lions Club; Stockgrowers Association), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 20)
    - T-Y (correspondents include Herman Talmadge, Governor of Georgia; Stanley Thill, Chairman Pondera County Republican Central Committee; Dan Thornton, Governor of Colorado; C. M. Wall, President Montana Chamber of Commerce; Leonard Young, Board of Railroad and Public Service Commission), 1953 (Box-folder 10 / 21)
    - A-E (correspondents include Walter Allen, Superintendent of Fisheries; T. L. Blau, Camera Press Limited; Darrell Coover; C. L. Crist, President KOOK; C. J. Doherty, Publisher The Times; K. G. Drew, Rainbow Ranch; Melvin Engles, Chairman Roosevelt County Republican Central Committee), 1954 (Box-folder 10 / 22)
    - F-L(correspondents include John S. Fine, Governor of Pennsylvania; J. W. Fry, Bice Truck Lines; J. C. Hickman, President Cascade County Taxpayers' League, Inc.; Herbert Hoover; W. J. Jameson; Ed Krebsbach, KGCK; J. Russell Larcombe, Phillips County News), 1954 (Box-folder 10 / 23)
    - M-Y (correspondents include Joseph W. Martin, Jr., Speaker House of Representatives; Republican National Committee; Allan Shivers, Governor of Texas; Floyd Underwood), 1954 (Box-folder 10 / 24)
    - A-B (correspondents include Forest Anderson; Victor Anderson, Governor of Nebraska; Erik Bottiger, Grand Secretary, Grand Lodge of Sweden; Norman Brunsdale, Governor of North Dakota; George Buchanan, Husky Oil Co.; Ken Byerly, Byerly Newspapers), 1955 (Box-folder 10 / 25)
    - C-E (correspondents include Huntley Childs, Yellowstone Park Company; L. A. Christensen, President Bank of Glacier County; Mary Condon, State Superintendent of Public Instruction; Darrell Coover; Gerald L. Crowley; Bryon Dunn, President National Bank of Commerce; Ellis Cattle Company), 1955 (Box-folder 10 / 26)
    - F-H (correspondents include James Flaherty, Great Falls Paper Co.; Roy Glover, Vice President and General Counsel Anaconda Copper Mining Co.; G. C. Hoyt), 1955 (Box-folder 11 / 1)
    - J-M (correspondents include Ben Larson, Publisher Circle Banner; J. H. McCallum, Vice President Harcourt, Brace and Co.; Montana Federation of Women's Republican Clubs), 1955 (Box-folder 11 / 2)
    - N-S (correspondents include National Broadcasting Company; Melvin Ruder, Hungry Horse News; Bess Reed, Missoula County Representative; R. D. Smith, Union Oil Company; E. B. Stanton, Vice President Northern Pacific Railway Co.), 1955 (Box-folder 11 / 3)
    - T-Z (correspondents include John F. M. Travis, Havre Daily News; Stewart Varn, Jocelyn-Varn Oil Co.; Western Air Lines, Inc.), 1955 (Box-folder 11 / 4)
    - A (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Staton Aby, President Kalman and Company, Inc.; I. A. Adams, Chairman Stillwater County Republican Central Committee; Anderson Clothing Company; W. A. Alexander, Shell Oil Company), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 5)
    - Appointments (includes Montana Highway Engineer and Montana Highway Commission), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 6)
    - B (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Marylou Bowman, Lake County Republican Central Committee; J. S. Brenner, Beaverhead County Senator; Norman Brunsdale, Governor of North Dakota; Ken Byerly, Byerly Publishing Co.;), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 7)
    - C (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Carter Oil Company; Glenn Chaffin, Hamilton Chamber of Commerce; Frank Clement, Governor of Tennessee; George Clevidence, Ravalli County Famers Union; Grover Cochran, U.S. Immigration-Naturalization Officers' Association; Darrell Coover), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 8)
    - D-E (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Wesley D'Ewart, Department of Agriculture; Frank Dougherty, Montana Association of County Commissioners; Robert Dwyer, Anaconda Company; J. G. Edmiston, Conrad National Bank; George Eikhoff, Board of County Commissioners Richland County), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 9)
    - F-G (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Minnie Fink, Glacier County Treasurer; B. A. Fisher, Hi-Ball Contractors, Inc.; Ray German, Oilmont; Leonard Gisvold, Vice President Northwestern National Bank of Minneapolis; James Glover, Jr.), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 10)
    - H-J (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Homer Hancock, Yellowstone County Representative; H. Harry Henderson, Ford Motor Co.; Matt Himsl, Chairman Flathead Republican Central Committee; W. H. Hornby Kalispell Lumber Co.; V. C. Hollingsworth, President Citizens State Bank; Larry L. Jones, Jr., Kirby Oil Industries, Inc.; Clark Jorgensen, Miles City Chamber of Commerce), 1956 (Box-folder 11 / 11)
    - K-L (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include R. F. Kitchingman, Great Falls Chamber of Commerce; Gladys Knowles, Republican National Committee; Carolyn Madden Larsen, Montana Conservation Council, Inc.; Frank Lausche, Governor of Ohio; Little People for an Honest Governor), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 1)
    - M (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Fred Martin, Park County News; Luis Munoz-Marin, Governor of Puerto Rico; K. J. McDonald, President Ravalli County Bank; A. F. McClaine, President Barmac Production Company), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 2)
    - N-P (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Walter C. Nye, dude Ranchers' Association; Lyle Onstad, Hope Lutheran Church; Catherine Pemberton, TA Ranch; J.C. Price; Dan C. Price, Sidney Chamber of Commerce), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 3)
    - R (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Republican National Committee; John W. Rodman, Parade Rest Ranch; Jerry Roe, President of the Young Republican Club; Thomas Ross, Blaine County Senator), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 4)
    - S (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Walter Sagunsky, Madison County Senator; E. J. Scheibe, Superintendent Texaco Petroleum Products; Sherman Smith, Secretary-Manager Helena Chamber of Commerce; Robert Sullivan, Dean School of Law Montana State University; (Rev) Edgar E. Swanson, Evangelical Mission Covenant Church of America), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 5)
    - T-V (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include John Tenge, President Midland National Bank; Ernest Thompson, Texas Railroad Commissioner; Union Oil Company of California), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 6)
    - W-Z (primarily congratulations on reelection; correspondents include Kay Watson, Cascade County Women's Republican Club; Western Airlines; R. H. Wiedman, Chairman Lake County Republican Central Committee; Robert Wilcox, President Miles City Chamber of Commerce; G. W. Yoder, Yoder Motor Company), 1956 (Box-folder 12 / 7)
    - A-B (correspondents include Jim Annin, Veteran's Hospital; William Baillie, State Chairman Montana Young Republicans John Ray Bliss, Chairman Republican State Central and Executive Committee; Burke, Chairman Metals Bank and Trust Co.), 1957 (Box-folder 12 / 8)
    - C-D (correspondents include E. J. Callaghan, Director Veterans' Welfare Commission; Frank Connelly; George N. Craig, Governor of Indiana; John Davis, Governor of North Dakota; Walt Disney, Walt Disney Production), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 1)
    - E-G (correspondents include J. W. Emmert, Glacier National Park; F. X. Faust, Chairman Forsyth Chamber of Commerce Hi-Way Commerce; Joe Foss, Governor of South Dakota; Joseph M. Gilmore, Bishop of Helena), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 2)
    - H-L (correspondents include Ben Hagerman, Yellowstone County Commissioner; A. W. Heidel, President Powder River County Bank; Rowland Kirks, National Automobile Dealers Association; Horace Koessler, Intermountain Lumber Co.; Herschel Loveless, Governor of Iowa), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 3)
    - M (correspondents include W. S. Mather, Chairman Musselshell County Republican Central Committee; Betty Maxey McKean, Sons and Daughters of Montana Pioneers; F. L. McPhail, Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education; Ed Mechem, Governor of New Mexico), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 4)
    - N-R (correspondents include Richard Nixon, Vice-President of United States; Northwest Airlines Inc.; Northwestern Life Insurance Co.; Phillips Petroleum Co.; Roland Renne, President Montana State College; Charles Russell, Governor of Nevada ), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 5)
    - S-T (correspondents include Milward Simpson, Governor of Wyoming; Robert Smylie, Governor of Idaho; C. H. Steele, Anaconda Company; William Stratton, Governor of Illinois; K. Richard Sturm, Elkhorn Oil Company, Inc.; Ken Todd, Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Co.), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 6)
    - U-Z (correspondents include Union Oil Company of California; Burton K. Wheeler, Montana Senator; Del E. Webb Construction Co.; Bill Zadick, City Editor Great Falls), 1957 (Box-folder 13 / 7)
    - A-C (correspondents include Arras Tank Co.; Ken Byerly School of Journalism University of North Carolina; Dean Chaffin, National Automobile Dealers Association; J. W. Corwin, Stillwater County Republican Central Committee), 1958 (Box-folder 13 / 8)
    - D-G (correspondents include Terrell Drinkwater, President Western Airlines; C. J. Doherty, Publisher Missoula Times; J. W. Emmert, Director of Idaho State Parks; Edward Fike, President of Fike Newspapers), 1958 (Box-folder 14 / 1)
    - H-L (correspondents include Helena Public Schools; Frank Hemingway, Mutual Broadcasting Company; Herbert Waldo Hines, President Rocky Mountain College; George Lund, President First National Bank), 1958 (Box-folder 14 / 2)
    - M-R (correspondents include Edwin Mechem, Governor of New Mexico; Montana Power Co.; Montana State University; Glenn Nielson, President Husky Oil Co.; Clarence Olson, American Legion; Republican National Committee; Douglas Rigg, Warden Minnesota State Prison), 1958 (Box-folder 14 / 3)
    - S-Z (correspondents include Fred Seaton, Secretary of the Interior; Robert Stevens; Charles Thronson, President Montana Bank; Ann Wolk, Montana Federation of Women's Clubs; Bill Zadick, Great Falls Tribune), 1958 (Box-folder 14 / 4)
    - A-Z (correspondents include Price Daniel, Governor of Texas; T. F. Haines, Montana State Food Distributors; Montana Power Co.), 1959 (Box-folder 14 / 5)
    - Duluth Seaway Dedication, 1959 (Box-folder 14 / 6)
    - Governor's Retirement Announcement, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14 / 7)
    - A-E (correspondents include Frank Banes, Chairman Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations; J. Caleb Boggs, Governor of Delaware; Bert Combs, Governor of Kentucky; Richard Cook, Editor Ethyl News; Leo Ellingson, Radio Program Director-KFBB), 1960 (Box-folder 14 / 8)
    - Congratulatory Letters on Governorship, 1960 (Box-folder 14 / 9)
    - F-L (correspondents include Lee Ford, Chairman of the Board of Great Falls National Bank; Harold Handley, Governor of Indiana; Norbert Hruby, Associate Dean University of Chicago; Joe Joffe, Superintendent Yellowstone National Park; Gladys Knowles, Republican National Committee; J. W. Liddell, Vice President Continental Oil Co.), 1960 (Box-folder 14 / 10)
    - M-Y (correspondents include E. R. McFarland, President, Kainai Chieftainship; Richard Nixon; William Quinn, Governor of Hawaii; Nelson Rockefeller, Governor of New York; Robert Timm, Republican National Committee), 1960 (Box-folder 15 / 1)
  - Correspondence Outgoing
    - Don Knutson (re Truth or Consequences TV show stunt), undated (Box-folder 15 / 2)
    - Thank You Letters, 1952 (Box-folder 15 / 3)
  - Legal Documents
    - Union Contract: State Tuberculosis Sanitarium, 1960 (Box-folder 15 / 4)
  - Press Releases
    - Editorials re Montana State Prison, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 15 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous (re appointments, legislative bills and agendas, State budget, federal-state relations), 1953-1960 (Box-folder 15 / 6)
  - Reports
    - "Earthquake and Slide at Madison Canyon" by State Highway Dept., 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 7)
    - State Penal Institutions Survey, 1957 (Box-folder 15 / 8)
  - Speeches
    - Address to the Montana Federation of Labor (Chadwick H. Smith), 1955 (Box-folder 15 / 9)
    - Annual Western Montana Air Show, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 10)
    - Boy Scout Ceremony, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 11)
    - Boy Scouts, undated (Box-folder 15 / 12)
    - Carter County Cattle and Sheep Grower Association, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 13)
    - Central Montana Highway Association, 1957, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 14)
    - Chinook Lincoln Day Talk, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 15)
    - Christmas Message, 1953, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 16)
    - Columbia Basin Inter-Agency Committee, 1957 (Box-folder 15 / 17)
    - Columbia Development Legislation Before Senate Committee on Public Works Subcommittee, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 18)
    - Commencement Address, "Help Yourself," Rocky Mountain College, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 19)
    - Community Development Conference, undated (Box-folder 15 / 20)
    - Congratulatory Message to KGVO 27th Anniversary, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 21)
    - County Commissioners, 1954-1957, undated (Box-folder 15 / 22)
    - Cut Bank Chamber of Commerce, 1960 (Box-folder 15 / 23)
    - Dedication, Anaconda Aluminum Company Plant, Columbia Falls, 1955 (Box-folder 15 / 24)
    - Dedication, Alberta Tourist Information Station, St. Mary's, 1956 (Box-folder 15 / 25)
    - Dedication, Bannack State Park, 1954 (Box-folder 15 / 26)
    - Dedication, Canyon Ferry Dam, undated (Box-folder 15 / 27)
    - Dedication, Diamond Match Company, Superior, 1953 (Box-folder 15 / 28)
    - Dedication, Forsyth Bridge, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 29)
    - Dedication, Fred Robinson Bridge, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 30)
    - Dedication, Galen Chapel, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 31)
    - Dedication, Glendive Bridge, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 32)
    - Dedication, Lewis and Clark Cavern State Park, 1954 (Box-folder 15 / 33)
    - Dedication, Livingston Memorial Hospital, 1955 (Box-folder 15 / 34)
    - Dedication, Miles City Bridge, 1957 (Box-folder 15 / 35)
    - Dedication, Montana-Dakota Utilities Plant, Sidney, 1958 (Box-folder 15 / 36)
    - Dedication, Montana School of Mines Building, undated (Box-folder 15 / 37)
    - Dedication, Montana State College Fieldhouse, 1957 (Box-folder 15 / 38)
    - Dedication, Noxon Dam, Thompson Falls, 1956 (Box-folder 15 / 39)
    - Dedication, Noxon Rapids Dam, undated (Box-folder 15 / 40)
    - Dedication, Senator Bill Cowan, undated (Box-folder 15 / 41)
    - Dedication, Terry Bridge, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 1)
    - Dedication, United States Army Reserve Training Center, 1958 (Box-folder 16 / 2)
    - Dedication, Van-Evan Company, Plentywood Plant, undated (Box-folder 16 / 3)
    - Dedication, "Whoop-Up Trail", 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 4)
    - Dedication, William Wylie Galt Hall, Great Falls, 1958 (Box-folder 16 / 5)
    - Delegates at the Republican National Convention, 1960 (Box-folder 16 / 6)
    - DeMolays Attending State Conclave of DeMolay, 1955 (Box-folder 16 / 7)
    - Excerpt from Governor's Message to Legislative Assembly, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 8)
    - Farmers Day of Greater Moorhead Days, 1960 (Box-folder 16 / 9)
    - Feeder Airline Service for Eastern Montana and North Dakota, undated (Box-folder 16 / 10)
    - Fellow Governors, undated (Box-folder 16 / 11)
    - Fellow Republicans Regarding Voting for President Eisenhower (incomplete), undated (Box-folder 16 / 12)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary of Sanders County, 1956 (Box-folder 16 / 13)
    - Forestry Meeting, undated (Box-folder 16 / 14)
    - Girls State Graduation, Willson Junior High School, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 15)
    - Governor's Day at National Guard Camp, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 16)
    - Governor's Greeting, Opening Business Session, undated (Box-folder 16 / 17)
    - Governor's Message to the Montana Legislative Assembly, 1955, 1957, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 18-20)
    - Governor's, Omaha Nebraska, 1955 (Box-folder 16 / 21)
    - Governor's Reelection Campaign, undated (Box-folder 16 / 22)
    - Ground-Breaking Ceremony, Carroll College, 1957, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 23)
    - Hamilton Chamber of Commerce, 1956 (Box-folder 16 / 24)
    - Harlem, Montana (regarding Governor Aronson's campaign reelection promises to Harlem), 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 25)
    - Highway Department Revenue, 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 26)
    - Highway Notes for Governor's Conference, Chicago, Illinois, 1955 (Box-folder 16 / 27)
    - Ike Night, undated (Box-folder 16 / 28)
    - Industrial Development Clinic, Billings, 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 29)
    - Intermountain States, Regarding Tourist Travel, 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 30)
    - Interstate Oil Compact Commission, New Orleans, 1959 (Box-folder 16 / 31)
    - Keynote, Bismarck, North Dakota, 1956 (Box-folder 16 / 32)
    - Keynote, Montana Republican Convention, Helena, 1954, undated (Box-folder 16 / 33)
    - Members of Boys State, Dillon, 1953 (Box-folder 16 / 34)
    - Members of Girls State, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 16 / 35)
    - Missouri Basin Inter-Agency Meeting, Sidney, 1954 (Box-folder 16 / 36)
    - Missouri River States Committee, Topeka, Kansas, 1953 (Box-folder 16 / 37)
    - Montana AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box-folder 16 / 38)